<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-31T17:23:56-06:00</updated><id>https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Jeffrey’s Jammin’ Blog</title><subtitle>A personal home for everything Jeffrey.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Project Feature Plans</title><link href="https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/2023/01/31/project-feature-plans.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project Feature Plans" /><published>2023-01-31T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-31T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/2023/01/31/project-feature-plans</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[|Category |Expectation| Explanation/Response| |-|-|-| |Program Purpose and Function |Describes the purpose of the program, describes the program’s functionality, and can take an input and return an output. |The purpose of this program is to provide the user and specifically small businesses to manage their inventory and stock through a streamlined method of inventory organization |Data Abstraction |Shows how data has been stored in a collection and shows data from that collection as it contributes to the overall purpose of the program. |Identifies the name of a variable representing the collection being used and describes what the data contained in the collection represents in the program. Our program abstracts data through data implementation which is accessed in a backend database. The purpose of this database is to store information about a user - be it their inventory, details, and stock - and these values should be able to be used in our program and construct a usable application where users can store and view details and inputs |Managing Complexity |Shows a collection of data that manages complexity. |Explains an alternative method that would have been more complex and explains why that method could not be used or how it would have to be written differently. There will be a multitude of ways to keep track/organizing inventory. Whether it’s searching for certain products, tracking location, or inserting details, the complexity is visible |Procedural Abstraction |Shows a student-developed procedure with at least one parameter that has an effect on the functionality of the procedure, and shows where that procedure is called. |Describes how the procedure contributes to the functionality of the program. This will be found in each and every one of our features, as we will need to develop the right code in order for these features to work |Algorithm Implementation |Includes a student-developed algorithm that includes sequencing, selection, and iteration. |Explains how the algorithm works in detail enough to where someone could recreate it. Listing inventory into a detailed table that stores the inventory’s information will have sufficient algorithms to fit this criteria. |Testing |Describe two calls to the selected procedure in response 3c. Each call must pass a argument that causes different outputs. |Describes conditions being tested by each call. Identifies the result of each call. We will test two different features in each section, which test certain conditions and output different results. CPT Each team member will be programming a special feature for the management system, so the individual create performance tasks will be focused on the respective features. For the n@tm project, we plan on intertwining each feature together to build one large application.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Title</title><link href="https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/2023/01/31/CPT-feature.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Title" /><published>2023-01-31T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-31T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/2023/01/31/CPT-feature</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Title</title><link href="https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/2023/01/30/yikers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Title" /><published>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/2023/01/30/yikers</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">APCSP 1/30/23 MC Practice Results</title><link href="https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/jupyter/python/tri2/misc/2023/01/30/APMC-Test-Corrections.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="APCSP 1/30/23 MC Practice Results" /><published>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/jupyter/python/tri2/misc/2023/01/30/APMC-Test-Corrections</id><author><name></name></author><category term="jupyter" /><category term="python" /><category term="tri2" /><category term="misc" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Big Ideas 5.1 and 5.2</title><link href="https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/jupyter/python/java/tri2/concept/student_learning/human_prep/2023/01/24/computers-and-dopamine.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Big Ideas 5.1 and 5.2" /><published>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-24T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://thegerbil21.github.io/firstfastpages/jupyter/python/java/tri2/concept/student_learning/human_prep/2023/01/24/computers-and-dopamine</id><author><name></name></author><category term="jupyter" /><category term="python" /><category term="java" /><category term="tri2" /><category term="concept" /><category term="student_learning" /><category term="human_prep" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry></feed>